Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram Ram
Ram Champion Champion Champion Champion Champion Champion Champion Champion Hoti
and all right guys so now
I request each and everybody
to please be present where they are.
Now we are going for the national anthem before we
move further for the final match.
I request the DJ person to please play
the national anthem now
pene
us side rakho we go
national now
janagana mana adhinayak jai jai
he Bharat bhagya vidhata
Punjab Sindhu Gujarat Maratha Davinga Himachal Yamuna
Ganga ul Jaldh taranga then shubh
naam me jage tab shubh
aashirwad rahe tab jai daata jana gana mangal dayak jai he
Bharat bhagya vidhata jai ho jai ho jai ho jai jai jai jai ho jai mata
ki jai.   Do
n't pull anywhere, there should be no background.   The
table is up
alright so here we are all set for the final
battle
and team WTW Warriors have had the toss
and they have elected to bat first in this
final game and this is going to be a right
over game only and let's go for the best let's go
for a close and let's go for an interesting
match